# Janardhana Nadupuru

+91 8500490186 | johnnadupuru186@gmail.com

#### PROFILE SUMMERY

Innovative front-end web developer with a strong background in the software industry. Proficient in HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, React.js, MySQL, Redux, Hooks and more. Experienced in building cross-browser compatible, accessible, responsive websites and REST API integration.

### **SKILLS**

**Programming Languages:** JavaScript, python, Object Oriented Programming(OOPs)

Web Development: HTML, CSS ,Bootstrap, React.js, Redux, Rest API ,Tailwind CSS, Node JS, Sql, PostgreSql

Soft Skills: Communication, Analytical and Problem-Solving, Team Work, Time Management & Adaptability.

### **PROJECTS**

# Satyadeep Foundation (https://foundation-jeze.vercel.app)

I have doing internship, they gave a task to create sample foundation website. I did create sample foundation website to collect some content from the internet.

### E-Commerce Website (https://j-mart-ten.vercel.app/)

I chose React as the core framework for its component-based architecture and the ability to efficiently update and render components.

Redux Toolkit was instrumental in managing complex state management, ensuring a consistent and predictable user experience.

Axios was used for making HTTP requests to retrieve and send data to the server. The website is responsive and adapts seamlessly to various screen sizes and devices

# Portfolio website (https://new-portfolio-vite.vercel.app)

I did create my Portfolio using React.JS . In this portfolio I used zustand library for state management and creating dark and white theme we can select moon icon. Change colour of text we can select on the colour text at top right on web page.

### Sample Contact List Redux toolkit (https://contact-list-roan-two.vercel.app)

Create a sample project for learning redux and redux tool kit. These project helps to well known about redux.

# **Dignity of Nobel demo site (https://dignityofnoble.org/)**

In this project, I developed Digital Plotforms and About Us these pages and I supported to develop many pages

## **INTERNSHIP**

Organization: Dignity of Nobel,

**Duration:** 6 Months,

Role: Full Stack Developer Intern,

Responsibilities: Worked as support in various projects

I improve react web developing skills and getting knowledge on axios, redux, authentication process. In

Backend Node JS improve model view controller skills.

# **EDUCATION**

Nxtwave Disruptive Technologies	Sep '22 - Ongoing
Industry Ready Certification in Full-stack Development	
B.Tech, Rajahmundry B Tech (Bachelor of Technology)_Mechanical Engineering (ME) (65.0%)	2012 - 2016
RK Junior College, Vizianagaram	2010 - 2012
Intermediate_MPC (87.0%)	

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Bandaru Bio Medicals (Service Engineer)

May 2021 – Feb 2023

Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh

Sales and service Electrolytes and ABG analysers

Divis laboratories (Production traine engineer)

May 2018 - Jan 2021

Nalgonda, Telangana

Following production Raw materail indents and following maintenance production equipments